(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T00:36:58.659486",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
ふたりはプリキュア
The two of us are Pretty Cure!
一難去ってまた一難 ぶっちゃんけありえない
Facing hardship after hardship, we break right through!
制服着ててもふたりは むっちゃくちゃタフだし
Even in uniform, we're totally tough!
お互いピンチを乗り越えるたび 強く近くなるね
Whenever we overcome a pinch together, we grow closer and stronger!
yeah, your best, my best 生きてるんだから
Your best, my best! We're living it up,
失敗なんてメジャじゃない
so failure is no big deal!
笑う門に福来るでしょ ネガティブだってぶっ飛ぶ
Good luck comes to those who smile—send those negative vibes flying!
命の花咲かせて思いきり
Let the flower of life bloom to the fullest,
もっとバリバリ
living even more vibrantly!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
(you're my best friend)
ふたりはプリキュア
The two of us are Pretty Cure!
たまには放課後のほほんとおしゃべり very time
Sometimes chatting away after school for a very long time...
ウワサは恋する乙女のビタミン剤だもん
Rumors are the vitamin for a girl in love!
夜闇に浮かんだ虹のかけ橋
The rainbow bridge floating in the dark night
ここに降下して奇跡
brings a miracle right down here!
yeah, your best, my best 全力だから
Your best, my best! Giving it our all,
友情愛情最高
friendship and love are the best!
論より証拠の輝くえくぼ 必殺技でハートキュン
With a shining dimple and a killer move, we've got your heart!
瞳に星映して思いきり もっとキラキラ
Reflect the stars in your eyes and glitter even brighter!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
(you're my best friend)
ふたりはプリキュア
The two of us are Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
明日は明日の風吹く まじ意味わかんない
"Tomorrow is another day"—I seriously don't get what that means!
今しかできない宿題 頑張らなくっちゃ
I've got to work hard on the homework I have to do right now!
真逆のキャラでも合い通じてる
Even with opposite personalities, we connect—
夢を生きるチカラ
the power to live our dreams!
yeah, your best, my best 生きてるんだから
Your best, my best! We're living it up,
失敗なんてメジャじゃない
so failure is no big deal!
笑う門に福来るでしょ ネガティブだってぶっ飛ぶ
Good luck comes to those who smile—send those negative vibes flying!
命の花咲かせて思いきり
Let the flower of life bloom to the fullest,
もっとバリバリ
living even more vibrantly!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
(you're my best friend)
ふたりはプリキュア
The two of us are Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
ふたりはプリキュア
The two of us are Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
ふたりはプリキュア
The two of us are Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
明日は明日の風吹く まじ意味わかんない
Tomorrow is tomorrow's wind, so I really don't know why...
命しかできない宿題 頑張らなくちゃ
I have to do my best on today's homework!
真逆のキャラでも愛し合ってる
Even with opposite personalities, we understand each other—
夢を生きるチカラ
the power to live our dreams!
yeah, your best, my best 生きてるんだから
Your best, my best! We're living it up,
失敗なんてメジャじゃない
so failure is no big deal!
笑う門に福来るでしょ ネガティブだってぶっ飛ぶ
Good luck comes to those who smile—send those negative vibes flying!
命の花咲かせて思いきり
Let the flower of life bloom to the fullest,
もっとバリバリ
living even more vibrantly!
(you're my best friend)
ふたりはプリキュア
The two of us are Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
ふたりはプリキュア
The two of us are Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure! Pretty Cure!
ふたりはプリキュア
The two of us are Pretty Cure!
誰かが好きだ あなたも好きだ
Someone I'm in love with, but I love you too!
もっとキュッと距離を埋めてみようよ
Let's try hard to close the distance even more!
働くのが好きだ サボるのは恋だ
I love working, but skipping work is romance!
えっとポットここで過ごしていたいよ
Let's just spend the time right here, just like this!
遥か遠くにユートピアが見えるよ
Far away, I can see utopia!
君の瞳の温泉に入ろう
Let's dive into the hot spring of your eyes!
魂ゴンとチャイムを打たれたなら (打たれちまったら)
If our souls beat in rhythm, (struck a chord,)
産毛ふわふわドリーム撫でられたなら (ONE ONE! SOMEONE ONE! ONE ONE!)
If our fluffy down is stroked in a dream, (One One! Someone One!)
進め！
Let's advance!
切なさほろ苦の真ん中いぬばれななら (いぬばれちまったら)
If we wander into a bittersweet middle, (into a bittersweet middle,)
くるぶしぐるぐる骨が感じているなら
If our ankles feel the bones spinning around,
走り出しましょう
let's start running!
踊る世界は義理人情
A dancing world of human ties and duties,
他人同士が笑い合う
where strangers smile at one another.
DNAは唐草模様
Our DNA is an arabesque pattern,
清く 正しく 美しく
pure, righteous, and beautiful.
何の前触れもない
Without any warning at all,
出逢いって不思議
encounters are so mysterious.
あてにならない第一印象 意外
Unreliable first impressions—what a surprise!
みんなのお祭り
It's everyone's festival,
手を打って踊ろう
so let's clap our hands and dance.
「イヨー」と言うからついてきて
Follow my lead when I shout "Iyo!"
ラムネ瓶をかざす朝陽 万華鏡
Morning sun and kaleidoscope through a ramune bottle.
パープル の夜明けは雅
A purple dawn is so graceful,
いつもの小径も三叉路も
and both the usual path and the fork in the road
世界の何処にだって続く
lead on anywhere in the world.
記号化などできない
You can't simply categorize
私達の明日
our tomorrow.
大切な人と笑ってられますように 未来
May we keep smiling with those dear to us in the future.
みんなみんな好きだ
Everyone loves it,
あなたは明日
and you are tomorrow.
そんな遠い視線 しないでくれ
Don't give me such a distant gaze.
くじけそうな時だ 頑張るのが愛だ
When you're about to break, trying your best is love—
ぐっと じっと こらえて
hold on tight and endure!
燃え上がってみたいよ
I want to burst into flames!
ほら宇宙（そら）に薔薇の楽園が見えるの
Look, can you see a rose garden in the universe?
結ばれた日のビュウ さきすわろう
Let's sit down and enjoy the view of the day we met.
叩かれ どことどこ ドラマ 戦われたなら
If we're struck, wherever it may be, in this dramatic fight,
叩かれちゃったら ぐずきが ジクジク ハート見すかされたなら
if we get battered and our aching hearts are seen right through—
汗をかきましょう
let's work up a sweat!
ひるこ 油断のりしゅろ ベリベリはかれたなら
If we let our guard down and get completely stripped away—
ほぐれちゃったら もののしげん ちもちわ ちくふくらんだなら
if we unravel and our feelings swell up,
走り出しましょう
let's start running!
さんわん さんわん さんわん さんわんえるさんわん
Three one, three one, three one, three one L...
まやかしの向こうにエデン 呪文のひらいたま（ま）
Eden beyond the illusion, as the spell opens up,
幻想わ（は）われてきらめく夜を破ろう
let's shatter the shimmering night of illusions!
ひとみにずうっと 二次元 くりぬかれたら
If our eyes are carved straight into two dimensions,
くりぬかれたら 指先 そろりと 本音をあばかれたら
if scooped out, fingertips gently revealing our true feelings—
寂しさほどのかみかみぬかれたら
if our loneliness is pierced right through,
見ぬかれたちょっと こまめにきれてささやかな形まわれたら
if we're seen through, neatly snapping and turning into a modest shape—
ウィンク飛ばしましょう
let's shoot a wink!
さんわん さんわん さんわん さんわんえるさんわん
Three one, three one, three one, three one L...
――始まる
—It begins.
世界は終わりの告げようとしている
The world is trying to proclaim its end.
誰にももう止められはしない
There is no one who can stop it anymore.
崩壊の交響曲が鳴り響いて 降る雨はまるで涙の音色
The symphony of destruction echoes, and the falling rain is like the tone of tears.
教えて 支配し支配され人達は
Tell me, why do people who rule and are ruled
いつかその心に憎しみを そして愛することを思い出せず
hold hatred in their hearts and forget how to love,
争うの? この歌が聴こえている
fighting each other? This song is echoing—
生命ある全ての者よ
to all living beings!
真実はいの胸の中にある
The truth lies deep within your heart.
世界は終わりを告げようとしている
The world is proclaiming the end,
誰にももう止められはしない
there is no one who can stop it now.
始まる
It's starting.
崩壊の交響曲が鳴り響いて
The symphony of destruction echoes,
降る雨はまるで涙の音色
the falling rain is like the tune of tears.
教えて
Tell me.
支配し支配され人達は
Why do those who rule and those being ruled
いつかその心に憎しみを…
take hatred into their hearts...
この歌が聴こえてる
This song can be heard
生命ある全ての者よ
by all beings with life.
真実人はあなたの胸の中にある
The truth lies within your heart.
嵐の海を行く時も
Even when going into a sea of storms,
決して怯えることのない強さをくれるから
it gives you the strength to never hesitate.
けれども進むほど風は強く
However, the stronger the wind blows as you advance,
希望の灯はわがれて消えていく
the candle of hope flickers and fades away.
灯火をよこせと奪い合い
"Give me your light," they steal from each other,
果てに人は殺し合う
and in the end, people kill one another.
涙なんてとうに枯れて
Tears have long since dried up.
気付いて
Realize this.
その目は互いを認めるため
Those eyes are to recognize each other,
その声は想いを伝えるため
that voice is to convey your feelings,
その手は大事な人と繋ぐためにある
and those hands are to hold your loved ones.
この歌が聴こえてる
This song can be heard
世界中の寄り辺なき者よ
by all the lost souls across the world.
希望はあなたの胸の中にある
Hope lies within your heart.
燃え盛る炎の中でも
Even amidst blazing flames,
決して傷付くことのない強さをくれるから
it gives you the strength to never be hurt.
その手で守ろうとしたものは愛する者だったのだろうか
Were those hands trying to protect the one you loved?
紅く染まったその手を眸めて
Gazing at your red-stained hands,
やっと自らしてきた愚かさを
you finally realize the foolishness you've done,
過ちと認めるその罪を
acknowledging your mistakes and sins,
とめどなくあふれるその涙を知る
and knowing the endless tears overflowing.
この歌が聴こえてる
This song can be heard
生命ある全ての者よ
by all beings with life.
真実人はあなたの胸の中にある
The truth lies within your heart.
嵐の海は静まった
The storm-tossed sea has calmed down,
失ったものは数えきれなくとも
even if the things you lost are countless.
この歌が聴こえてる
This song can be heard
世界中の寄り辺なき者よ
by all the lost souls across the world.
希望はあなたの胸の中にある
Hope lies within your heart.
悲しみの夜を超えるとき
When you overcome a night of sadness,
必ずあなたは生きていく強さを持てるから
you will surely have the strength to keep living.
社交辞令みたいな競争にも慣れてこんな日常を平和と見間違う
Accustomed to empty pleasantries, I mistake this daily life for peace.
ランブリング コースター 揺さぶられながら見失わないものは何だ?
As this rambling coaster jolts me, what is it that I mustn't lose sight of?
超天変地異みたいな狂騒にも慣れて
Accustomed to the cataclysmic madness,
こんな日常を平和と見間違う
I mistake my daily life for peace.
ランブリング コースター
Rambling coaster,
揺さぶられながら見失えないものは何だ?
What is it that I mustn't lose sight of?
平等主義の概念に飲まれて
Drunk on the concept of fundamental equalism,
心までがまるでエトセトラ
It feels like even my soul is kind of et cetera.
大嫌い 大好き ちゃんとしゃべんなきゃ
Love it or hate it, you gotta say it clearly,
人形とたして変わらないし
Or you're no different from a doll.
夜の街を往く人ばかりは
Crowds walking the streets at night,
嬉しそうだったり寂しそうだったり
Some seem happy, some seem lonely.
コントラストが五線譜を飛び回り
The contrast jumps around the staff lines,
歌とリズムになる
Creating song and rhythm.
マヌレードにシュガーソング ピーナッツ&ビターステップ
Marmalade and sugar song, peanuts and bitter step,
甘くて苦くて目が回りそうです
So sweet yet acrid, it makes my head spin!
南南西を目指してパーティを続けよう
Heading south-southwest to keep the party going,
世界中を驚かせてしまう夜になる
To make it a night that astonishes the world!
I feel 絶好調 連鎖になってリフレクト
I feel fantastic, reflecting it in a chain!
大前提 合理主義の線路にも慣れて
Accustomed to the strict logic of the elite,
僕らの道具になるさが
We become mere tools.
こっちを向いてよ 背を向けないでよ
Open your eyes, don't turn away,
それは正義にならないけど
Even if it's not the right path.
祭りはヤシのその外側で
Festivals are outside, that's all,
高ぶったままの状態で鳴き出しにしてしまうぞ
Just staying fired up inside.
たぶん明日のノーウ
If we turn tomorrow into words,
でも言葉にするものなら 季節の時は溢れ
The changing seasons overflow.
最高だってシュガーソング 合わせて満たして
It's the best! Sugar song, matching and filling it up,
シャッ閉ざしに夢をそこに映し出せ
Closing my eyes and projecting it down below!
欲しかったって全速で明日を駆け抜けなくちゃの
Running out of breath at top speed tomorrow,
ないてきみをほうむあぷでーとを果たしたなら
Updating yesterday's handbook if I've made it this far!
大前提 合理主義の線路にも慣れて
Accustomed to the strict logic of the elite,
僕らの道具になるさが
We become mere tools.
こっちを向いてよ 背を向けないでよ
Open your eyes, don't turn away,
それは正義にならないけど
Even if it's not the right path.
お祭り騒ぎのその外側で
The festival's outside, that's all,
高ぶったままのぞんで泣き出しにしてしまうぞ
Staying fired up inside.
たぶん明日のノーウ
If tomorrow becomes words,
でも言葉にするものなら 季節の時は溢れ
Even if zero has no meaning anymore,
鳴らし続けることだけが
Just continuing to tell the truth
僕たちを僕たちたらしめるお土産になる
Will become the souvenir that heals us.
急に間に回れどうにシュガーソング ピーナッツ&ビターステップ
Marmalade and sugar song, peanuts and bitter step,
生きてく理由をそこに映し出せ
The reason for living, reflecting it down below!
歩むことと遠く その距離が誇らしい
Proudly shouting our distance from each other,
世界中を驚かせて続けよう
Let's keep astonishing the whole world!
回り出せのシュガーソング ピーナッツ&ビターステップ
Marmalade and sugar song, peanuts and bitter step,
甘くて苦くて目が回りそうです
So sweet yet acrid, it makes my head spin!
南南西を目指してパーティを続けよう
Heading south-southwest to keep the party going,
世界中を驚かせてしまう夜になる
To make it a night that astonishes the world!
I feel 絶好調 連鎖になってリフレクト
I feel wretched, the chain of reflections goes on!
もう一回だって もう一回
Again and again, let's go!
Forever the melodies
Forever the melody goes on.
この瞳は鮮やかに舞う キミしか知覚しえない
All my eyes can see is you dancing brilliantly,
踏み込んで覚醒めする セカイへ
Step in, be awakened, head for the world!
Chase the world
俯きすぎて小さな僕だけの景色が
I'm aware of the painful stares.
僕だけの景色が
As we go on our way.
組み立てたジオラマの嘘だと合わせ辛い視点に気づいている
I will dash out to the future and get my hands on beauty,
走り出していく未来は 美しさを手に それぞれが翔べる場所を 問いかけていく
Asking about the places where each one of us can fly.
この瞳は鮮やかに舞う キミしか知覚しえない
All my eyes can see is you dancing brilliantly,
加速して初めて往ける 僕は僕の先へ
After accelerating, I can go my own way for the first time.
もっと昂く もっと強く キミに届きたい
Go higher, become stronger, I want to reach you!
踏み込んで覚醒めする Chasin' the world
Step in, be awakened, chasing the world!
この瞳は鮮やかに舞う キミしか知覚しえない
All my eyes can see is you dancing brilliantly,
加速して初めて往ける 僕は僕の先へ
After accelerating, I can go my own way for the first time.
もっと昂く もっと強く
Go higher, go stronger!
この瞳に届きたい
I want to reach those eyes,
踏み込んで目覚めるセカイへ
stepping in, heading to the awakening world!
Chase the world
幾億の迷宮すり抜けて
Slipping through countless labyrinths,
すり切れてしまった
I've worn them out completely.
諦めてしまえとゆう声が
The voice telling me to just give up
潜んだ壁を壊したがる
wants to break down the wall lurking in wait.
ひたむきに祈る声も闇に割れる夜
Even the earnest prayers shatter in the night's darkness,
叶わない残酷さを潜ませても
even harboring the cruelty of unfulfilled wishes.
この翼で思うよりも遥かに羽ばたく
With these wings, I will soar far beyond imagination,
抑えない鼓動が運命を進めるなら
if this uncontrollable heartbeat drives my fate forward.
願う前に戻る前にキミを抱きしめて
Before wishing, before turning back, I'll hold you tight
彼方へと羽ばたこう
and fly toward the distant horizon—
Changing your world
この瞳には鮮やかに舞うキミしか知覚出来ない
My eyes can only perceive you dancing brilliantly,
加速して初めて往ける僕は僕の先へ
accelerating to go beyond myself for the first time.
この翼で思うよりも遥かに羽ばたく
With these wings, I will soar far beyond imagination,
抑えない鼓動が運命を進めるなら
if this uncontrollable heartbeat drives my fate forward.
もっと高くもっと強くキミに届きたい 踏み込んで目覚める
Higher and stronger, I want to reach you, stepping in to awaken—
世界へ！
into the world!
メイさん来てくださって本当にありがとうございます！
May'n-san, thank you so much for coming!
ありがとうございます！2周年おめでとうございます！
Thank you so much! Congratulations on your 2nd anniversary!
ありがとうございます！もう嬉しすぎて、ちょっともう本当にびっくりしまして、本当にみんなびっくりしてます今！
Thank you so much! I'm so overjoyed, everyone's so surprised!
いや、嬉しいです、でもこうやってご一緒させてもらえて。いやもう緊張しました本当。
Oh, I'm so happy to perform together. I was really nervous.
だっていろんな、あの、例えば「ライオン」とか「イブザード」とかも歌っていただいてましたもんね、以前。
Because you've sung songs like "Lion" and "Northern Cross" before, right?
そんな、歌えてるんですね。
Oh, I've sung those?
「ライオン」は元々私たちふたりで歌わせて貰ってる楽曲なので、おひとりでね、あんなにまた違う風に歌えるなんてと思って、すごく嬉しく思ってます。
"Lion" is a song we originally sang together, so hearing you sing it alone was so wonderful.
いや、こちらこそ本当にありがとうございます！え、VTuberコラボが初めてだって、お伺いしたんですけど。
No, thank you so much! I heard this is your very first VTuber collab.
あ、そうなんですよ。なので、こうやって、あの、あと自分の楽曲を
Ah, that's right. So getting to have my own song...
他の歌い方でカバーしてくださって、一緒に歌うっていう経験も、実はお互いアーティスト同士のコラボも少なくて、自分の曲だと、はい。
covered by someone else and singing together is rare even among artists.
なので、今回の機械、かなり、はい、VTuberの方とのコラボっていう意味でもめちゃめちゃ特別ですし、本当に初めてがたくさん詰まったコラボでした。すごく嬉しいです。
So this opportunity is extremely special and full of firsts for me.
嬉しいです、ありがとうございます！え、なんか、めちゃめちゃ本当に緊張してて、なんかご挨拶に行くときとかも
I was really nervous. Even when I went to go greet you earlier...
「え、どうしようどうしよう」と思ってて、「え、なんかちょっと失礼がないようにしなきゃ」と思って、
thinking "What should I do?", making sure I wouldn't be rude.
で、ちょっとあのメイク中だってお伺いしてたんで、ガチャって開けたら、なんかあのメインさんがメイクまだされてる最中でで、
And when I opened the door, you were still in the middle of makeup,
その時に、メインがメインじゃない時なんですけど、って言ってて、まだなんか化粧水の後の乳液の段階だって、別々のメイになる前の状態で、
still at the lotion stage before transforming into "May'n", haha!
本当、いや本当に、でめちゃくちゃすっぴんなかったで、マジで安心しました！
Seeing that bare-faced moment actually made me so relieved!
いやいや、嬉しいです！本当にありがとうございました！
Haha, I'm so glad! Thank you so much!
本当に楽しかったです！ぜひまたまた、あの、今度コラボさせてください！
It was so much fun! Please let's collaborate again sometime!
ぜひぜひ、よろしくお願いします！ありがとうございました！
Absolutely, I'd love that! Thank you so much!
では、まだまだライブは続きますので、みなさんよろしくお願いします！ありがとうございました！バイバーイ！
Well, the live continues, so everyone please enjoy! Bye-bye!
放て! 心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえも置き去りにして
Fire away! Leave behind the future and the dreams engraved in your heart
限界など知らない 意味ない この力が光散らす
It knows no limits and has no meaning, my power radiating outward
その先に遥かな想いを
toward distant feelings far beyond!
歩いてきた この道を 振り返ることしか出来ないなら
If I can only look back on this path I've walked...
今ここで全てを壊せる
I could destroy it all right here and now.
闇に堕ちる街並み 人はどこまで立ち向かえるの?
How far can people stand against the streets descending into darkness?
加速するその痛みから 誰かをきっと守れるよ
I'm sure I can protect someone from that accelerating pain.
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way. Only my RAILGUN can shoot it.
今すぐ 身体中を 光の速さで 駆け巡った 確かな予感
Right now, a certain premonition raced through my body at the speed of light.
掴め! 望むものなら残さず 輝ける自分らしさで
Catch it! If it's your wish, don't leave it behind with your shining individuality.
信じているよ あの日の誓いを
I believe in the vow we made that day.
この瞳に光る涙 それさえも強さになるから
Even the tears glittering in these eyes will become my strength.
立ち止まる少しだけ 感じる切なさに 戸惑うなんて嘘はつかないよ
Standing still, I feel a slight pain; I won't lie and say I'm not confused.
穹に舞うコインが描く 放物線が決める運命
The parabola drawn by the coin dancing in the sky decides our fate.
打ち出した答えが今日も 私の胸を駆け巡る
The answer I shot out rushes through my heart again today.
Sparkling! The shiny lights awake true desire. only my railgun can shoot it. Kanarazu...
Sparkling! The shiny lights awake true desire. Only my railgun can shoot it without fail...
貫いてく迷うことなく 傷ついても走り続ける
Piercing through without hesitation, I'll keep running even if I'm hurt.
狙え! 凛と輝く視線は 狂いなく闇を切り裂く
Ready, aim! My dignified, shining gaze tears through the darkness without missing.
迷いなんて吹き飛ばせばいい この心が叫ぶ限り 誰ひとり邪魔などさせない
Blow away any hesitation! As long as my heart cries out, I won't let anyone get in my way.
僅かに舞う無数の願いは この両手に積み募っていく
The countless fleeting wishes dancing around pile up in both of my hands.
切り裂く闇に見えてくるのは 重く深く切ない記憶
What becomes visible in the tearing darkness is a heavy, deep, and painful memory.
色褪せてく現実に捉われる 絶望には負けたくない
Caught in a fading reality, I don't want to lose to despair.
私が今 私であることを 胸を張って全て誇れる!
Right now, I can proudly stand tall and be proud of who I am!
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way. Only my RAILGUN can shoot it.
今すぐ 身体中を 光の速さで 駆け巡った 確かな予感
Right now, a certain premonition raced through my body at the speed of light.
放て! 心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえも置き去りにして
Fire away! Leave behind the future and the dreams engraved in your heart.
限界など知らない 意味ない この力が光散らす
It knows no limits and has no meaning, my power radiating outward
その先に遥かな想いを
toward distant feelings far beyond!
儚く眠る私の願いは この両手にいつもってゆく
My fleeting, sleeping wishes I will always hold in these hands.
切り裂く闇に見えてくるのは 重く深く切ない記憶
What becomes visible in the tearing darkness is a heavy, deep, and painful memory.
色褪せてく現実に捉われる 絶望には負けたくない
Caught in a fading reality, I don't want to lose to despair.
私がいま 私であることを 胸を張って全て誇れる
Right now, I can proudly stand tall and be proud of who I am.
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way. Only my RAILGUN can shoot it.
今すぐ 身体中を 光の速さで 駆け巡った 確かな予感
Right now, a certain premonition raced through my body at the speed of light.
放て! 心に刻んだ夢を
Fire away! The dreams engraved in your heart,
未来さえも置き去りにして 限界など知らない 意味ない
leaving even the future behind, knowing no limits, meaningless...
この力が光散らす その先に遥かな想いを
This power scatters light toward distant feelings far beyond!
光散らす その先に遥かな想いを
Scattering light, toward distant feelings far beyond!
ゲストが今まではね普通だったんですけれど
Guests used to be pretty normal until now,
今回なんと先輩方を誘ったりあとMiiさんがね来ていただいたりするとなると結構スペシャルな1日になったんじゃないかなと思うんですが
but this time, inviting seniors and even having Mii-san come makes it quite a special day, don't you think?
どうだったりしようかびっくりしたでしょう絶対ゲスト予想当たらないと思ったんだよね
What do you think? Were you surprised? I bet you never guessed who the guests would be!
もうね5番の予想はね絶対外れると思って出しました。いじわるしましたすみません。
I put out the 5th guess knowing it would definitely be wrong. I was being mean, sorry.
え、ということですね、えーまぁまたステージの方もね色々作ってもらってめちゃめちゃ良かったんですが、
So, um, they made all sorts of stages for us and it was amazing,
こちらの振り返りのルームでお話しさせていただければと、甘えまーす！しっかり紹介したいのでめちゃめちゃいいですよでもね、めちゃめちゃいい！フェス会場！
but I'd love to talk about it here in this review room. I'm taking you up on that! I want to introduce it properly, it's so good, you know? It's seriously great! The festival venue!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
ではですね、配信もちょうど半分が終わったところなので、今日は企画を持ってきました。じゃじゃーん！せっかくのアニメフェスということで、
Now, since the stream is about halfway through, I brought a project today. Ta-da! Since it's a special anime festival...
せーの！サカマタ生アフレコイェーイ！
Ready, set! Sakamata Live Dubbing, Yay!
はい、こちらですね、ちょっとどういったものなのかというのを説明させてください。
Yes, let me explain what this is about.
え、今からですね、過去にも公開済みのホログラのVTRを流しながらサカマタが生アフレコをしていきたいと思います。
From now on, I'm going to do live dubbing over a previously released Hologra VTR.
まず最初は、こちらです！
First up is this!
はい、世界征服はじめましたです。覚えてますか？
Yes, "We started world domination." Do you remember?
それではまずは実際に投稿された映像の一部を見ていきましょう。どうぞ！
Now let's first take a look at a portion of the actual posted video. Here we go!
一刀両断 ぶった切る
Strike down and cut through with one stroke
終わりなき輪廻に迷い子らよ
Lost children in the endless samsara,
漆黒の翼で誘おう
I will invite you with pitch-black wings.
我ら、エデンの星を統べる
We rule the star of Eden.
今日は気分じゃないかもしれない
Maybe I'm not in the mood today.
作戦会議日和かもしれない
Maybe it's a good day for a strategy meeting.
今日の議題「 」
Today's agenda: " "
まずは
First is...
世界制服……
World domination...
足腰にね
on our legs...
オーロラライブを……
Aurora live...
だってこんな高いんだよ！ おい、インターン！
Because it's so high! Hey, intern!
寝てるね
She's sleeping.
口感をお猫様気取りやがって
Acting like a cat...
それ何のいみが……学ぶは真似ぶということ
What's the point of that? To learn is to imitate.
つまり何も分かってないね
In other words, you don't understand anything.
それも事実！もぐもぐ会議して
That's a fact too! Mumble-mumble meeting,
今夜の頭脳が必要そうだね。今夜！ 問題を解けるのはお前だけだ
We need brains tonight. Tonight! You're the only one who can solve the problem.
かすまくん！それ我が輩のセリフ！
Kasuma-kun! That's my line!
それ何ができるの？
What can that do?
大量のシャボンダマが出るよ
Tons of soap bubbles will come out.
何の意味が…
What's the point...
世界中の子供がこれに夢中になり、どこもかしこもシャボンダマまみれに
Children all over the world will be engrossed in this, and everywhere will be covered in soap bubbles.
世界がどんどんベトベトになっていき、風呂の回数が極端に増え
The world will get more and more sticky, the number of baths will increase drastically,
絶対使わないでね、油断したところを
Never use it, when you let your guard down
ホロックスが叩く。そうは習いんやろ。
holoX strikes. That's not what we learned.
遊ぶな！
Don't play around!
あれ？いろはちゃん？黒ータン？
Huh? Iroha-chan? Kuro-tan?
総帥、こちらに。
Souui, over here.
敵兵は１つ、単身で乗り込んでき奪ってはね
The enemy force is one, riding in solo...
目標は？
The target?
それわかんないかな！
You don't know that?!
誰か助けてー！
Somebody help me!
大丈夫ですよ、総帥。
It's alright, Souui.
風間いろは、坂マタ、接敵！
Kazama Iroha, Sakamata, engaging enemy!
すみません、まだ分かってないでしょ！
Excuse me, you still don't get it!
猫！
Cat!
いやー本当におなじみホログラにしたね。
Man, that really was the usual Hologra.
はい、でも今回のちょっとやった1本目はですね、セリフ少ない方なんですよ。
Yes, but the first one we just did has fewer lines.
で、ちょっとこの猫ずこうもなんとなく覚えてたんですけど、2本目めちゃくちゃセリフ多いんですよ、皆さん。こちら！
And, I kind of remembered this cat zuko part too, but the second one has an absurd amount of lines, everyone. Here it is!
実体の無い雑魚に負けるわけない！……よね？
"I'd never lose to some nobody with no real substance!" Right?
ってやつです。
That's the kind of bit it is.
では、また、実際の映像の一部を見てください。どうぞ。
Well then, let's watch part of the actual footage. Here you go!
真っ黒え！説明しよう。
Pitch black... Let me explain.
なんか起きたら夜になってて、誰もいないし帰りたいんだけど、
I woke up thinking it was night, and there's no one around, so I want to go home,
あ、鍵持ってないじゃん。
but I don't have my key, right?
さすがに閉じ込められるのはまずいなって。
Naturally, getting locked in is bad news, right?
だから帰るに帰れないわけよ。
So, there's no way I can go home!
とりあえず……
For now...
いやあ、マジでね、全然覚えてないすけど、
Man, I seriously don't remember this at all, haha.
ちょっとね、見ていきたいと思います。クソほど知り尽くしてるんで、
Let's go back and watch it again. It's crazy how much I know about this.
あの、なんか声が遅れて聞こえてきたりしたらね、それはみんなのせいです。行きます！
So, if my voice is a bit delayed or lagging, it's everyone else's fault! Here we go!
真っ黒え！説明しよう。
Pitch black! Let me explain.
なんか起きたら夜になってて、誰もいないし帰りたいんだけど、あ、鍵持ってないじゃん。
I woke up thinking it was night, and there's no one around, so I want to go home, but I don't have my key, right?
さすがに閉じ込められるのはまずいなって。
Naturally, getting locked in is bad news, right?
だから帰るに帰れないわけよ。
So, there's no way I can go home!
とりあえず……
For now...
あれ？
Huh?
あれ？スリッパの音？
Wait, is that a sound?
どこで喋ってらっしゃるんですか、あなた。
Wait, where are you talking from, pal?
え、スリッパの音？あれ？
Huh? Slippers? Wait...
まっ、タピオカミルクティー最近キツそうだなもんね。
Wait, tapioca milk tea sounds so good right now!
びっくりした。つまりこの部屋にいるのは……
That scared me. So, the one in this room is...
You & Ray!
近づいてくるな！
Don't come near me!
だから、しかし、し、し、し、肉体のない雑魚に負ける坂本ってわけ……キャー！
So, however— Wait, wait, wait! I can't lose to someone with no physical body, wait!
わしじゃよ。小賢しい影の音が聞こえたのでな。
"It's just me. I heard your squeaky little shadow, you see."
さかまたー！
Sakamata!
真っ黒え！
Pitch black!
ループって怖い！
Time loops are scary!
いや、完璧でしたね！
Man, that was perfection!
よかった！
That was great.
もう一寸の狂いもなく、はい、行けましたね。大丈夫でしたね？
That was literally on another level. We made it, right? We're good, right?
はい、というわけで、さかまた生アフレコでした！いぇーい！
Alright, with that said, Sakamata's live voice acting is done! Yay!
でですね、この後、ライブがラストスパートに向けて、
Well, you see, after this, we're heading into the last spurt of the live,
ちょっと加速していくんですけど、
so we're gonna pick up the pace!
まだまだ盛り上がって行きまーす！いぇーい！はい！
Let's keep the hype going even more! Let's go! Yay!
ではですね、この後、なんとゲストの方々にも生配信です。参戦していただきまーす！
Now then, after this, we're actually going to have a live stream with our guests!
ちょっとね、ゲストの皆さんも含めて一緒に応援していってください！
Let's all cheer together, including our guests!
それは、ラストスパート最初のゲストはこの方です！
So, the very first guest for the last spurt is this person!
森さん！
Mori-san!
こんばんは！Calliセンパイ！
What's up? Calli-senpai!
デスデス。森カリオペです。What's up, クロエちゃん？
What's up? Mori Calliope is here. What's up, Chloe-chan?
いや、もうめっちゃ緊張してましたけど、
Man, I was so nervous,
Calliセンパイが堂々とこう来てくれて、安心しました、今。
but Calli-senpai came out looking so cool, I can finally relax now!
余裕、余裕ですよ。
You're way too relaxed.
ちょっと楽しみましょうよ。
Let's enjoy this!
Let's go, 激しくかまそうぜ！Let's rock!
Let's go, let's rock this!
Counteraction rising
Yeah, we are ready for the punch line
There's no use with all your gimmicks
So check this out!
Login you damned one's
Crush the wont you compromise
The noise comes we are ready to bow
What about the antidote for the jammed and hypnotized
Rend the lie that covers
Who's the real sucker now?
咲き乱れた花のように鮮やかな痛み抱き
Like a blooming, scattering flower, holding a vivid pain,
佇む街を抜け迷いのセリフは捨て
making my way through the bustling streets, leaving hesitant words behind.
還らない声よ響け
Let the unreturning voice ring out!
We say wow wow wow wow
Database database Just living in the database wow wow
The wall of pure fiction's cracking in my head
And the addiction of my world still spreads
In the database database I'm struggling in the database wow wow
It doesn't even matter if there is no hope As the madness of the system grows
Crack in the key for the real clue
Mass redemption reigning on but we know we've been longing for this
Cut it out the plot that deceived you
Drop the rebel sound shut the system down Reveal the never found now
引き裂かれとしたとしても虚構とも現実とも見えるガレキの中で戦い続けるだけ
Even if torn apart, whether illusions or reality, I keep fighting amidst visible rubble.
Counteraction rising
Yeah we are ready for the punch line
咲き乱れた花のように
Like flowers blooming in reckless abandon,
鮮やかな痛み抱き
embracing vibrant pain,
佇む街を抜け 迷いのセリフは捨て
I slip through bustling streets and cast away hesitant words.
還らない声よ響け
Let my unreturned voice echo!
database database
just living in the database wow wow
just living in the database, woah-oh!
the wall of pure fiction's cracking in my head
and the addiction of my world still spreads
in the database database
i'm struggling in the database wow wow
I'm struggling in the database, woah-oh!
it doesn't even matter if there is no hope
just say wow wow wow wow
just say, woah-oh-oh-oh!
Hey wait a minute, what happened? The data's wrong! Come on!
引き裂かれたとしても 虚構とも現実とも
Even if I'm torn apart, amid fiction and reality,
見えるガレキの中で 戦い続けるだけ
amid visible rubble, I will keep on fighting.
get damn all from big airheads
yeah you get
時に計算高さは蛇足だ calculator
Sometimes excessive calculation is just a needless calculator,
統計にゆさぶられたまま消えていった
swept away by statistics and vanishing into nothingness.
そうなりたきゃないけ database
If you don't want to end up like that, database,
だけに頼らず磨け 自分のペース
don't just rely on it—grind at your own pace!
get damn all from big airheads
yeah you get damn all from big airheads
database database
just living in the database wow wow
just living in the database, woah-oh!
the wall of pure fiction's cracking in my head
and the addiction of my world still spreads
in the database database
i'm struggling in the database wow wow
I'm struggling in the database, woah-oh!
it doesn't even matter if there is no hope
as the madness of the system grows
database database
just living in the database wow wow
just living in the database, woah-oh!
database database
just say wow wow wow wow
just say, woah-oh-oh-oh!
はい、ということで、え、カリ先パイをお迎えしてのデータベイスにしました。
Alright, so we've welcomed Calli-senpai for this database performance!
ではでは、最後のゲスト……呼んじゃおうかな、どうしようかな。呼んじゃい！って言ってもありますかね？
Now then, should we call out the final guest? Who should it be?
呼んじゃお！きちゃった！
Let's call them! She's here!
きちゃった！
She's here!
どなたですか？星街すいせいです！
Who could it be? Hoshimachi Suisei!
よろしくお願いします！
Thanks for having me!
まあ、ちょっと疲れてるんじゃないですか？
Well, aren't you guys a little tired?
いやいや、まだまだっすよ。
No way, not at all!
いけるんですか？いけますよ！
Can you keep going? Absolutely!
じゃあ行ってやりましょうよ。ぶちかまそうあの曲を！
Then let's go for it! Let's smash out that song!
いかざあ！いかざあ！
Let's go! Let's go!
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
because truthfully, I'm crazy!
白鳥たちはそう 見えないところでバタ足するんです
'Cause even swans, you know, flutter their legs out of sight.
本能に順従 忠実 翻弄も重々承知
True to my instincts, fully aware of all the teasing,
舟上洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
the future is bright... which is why I take a break sometimes.
この目ですしっかり見定めて
Ascertain it carefully with your own eyes,
行き先地図上マークして
and mark it on your map.
近道あればそれが王道
A shortcut is the royal road,
はしゃる翼があれば上等
and wings to flutter with are even better!
ヤバ 爪割れた グルーで補修した
Crap, broke a nail, patched it up with glue,
それとなんとなく達成感
and somehow that gives a sense of achievement.
大事なことは自分 かわがること
The most important thing is to cherish yourself;
自分を愛さないと 他人も愛せない
you can't love others unless you love yourself.
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
because truthfully, I'm crazy!
能ある鷹はそう
'Cause even the skilled hawk, you know,
見えないところにピック隠すんです
hides its picks where they can't be seen.
想像に一生懸命 現実は絶体絶命
Dreaming with all my might, reality is do-or-die,
発展途上だし...
still under development...
だからふいにピッチ外れるんです
which is why I suddenly go off pitch.
その目に映らないただそれだけで
Even when it's out of sight,
やる気はメーター振り切って
my drive maxes out the meter.
いつでも全力で夢見て
Always dreaming with all my heart,
そのぶん全力で眠って
and sleeping just as hard in return.
やりちょい痩せた 調子づいて暴食した
Awesome, got a bit thinner, then binged happily—
それがなんで? 敗北感
why does that feel like defeat?
すかさずに目標下方修正して
Quickly lower your expectations,
柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
flexibility and adaptability win the day!
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
because truthfully, I'm crazy!
孔雀たちはそう
'Cause even peacocks, you know,
ここぞというとき美を見せるんです
wait until the moment is right to show their beauty.
五臓六腑 満身創痍
Body and soul battered and bruised,
望遠はそう心霊神 誘惑多発だし...
temptations are everywhere...
だからやけにいそがしくなっちゃうんです
which is why we get so terribly distracted.
ヤバ まさか赤点Red Point!? いや ギリギリクリア!
Crap, is that a red mark? No, barely in the clear!
それだけでなんか達成感
That alone gives a sense of achievement.
大事なことは自分 かわがること
The most important thing is to cherish yourself;
自分を愛さないと 他人も愛せない
you can't love others unless you love yourself.
そんないくつもないけれど
There aren't that many, but...
だってやる気はメーター振り切って
My motivation has maxed out the meter!
いつでも全力で夢見て
Dreaming with all my might at any time,
その分全力で眠って
And sleeping with all my might just as much.
やりすぎちゃった 調子づいて驕った
I went too far, got carried away and arrogant.
それだけでなんで？敗北感
Just from that, why? A sense of defeat.
すかさずに目標 下方修正して
Quickly lowering my targets downwards,
欠かさずにも目標を
Without fail, my goals...
過保護修正して 柔軟に
Adjusting them over-protectively, flexibly.
臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
Adapting on the fly, changing seven ways wins!
Freedom! So you are lazy!
だって本当はcrazy
Because I'm actually crazy!
朽雀たちはそう
The fading sparrows are like that...
おもむろに憂うときびを見せるんです
Showing sternness when solemnly lamenting.
そろそろ満身創痍
Before long, battered and bruised,
野望は細心冷静
Ambitions are meticulous and calm.
誘惑脱出作戦
A temptation escape operation!
だからやけに気淑くだけじゃおんぼろ
That's why being overly refined alone is shabby.
さあ待たせた！
Now, you've kept me waiting!
ここで決着をつけようか！
Let's settle this right here!
行きましょうか！
Shall we go?!
最初はグー！じゃんけんぽい！愛こそすべて！
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot! Love is everything!
ガンバマサカればい いやぎりくりあ
Let's do our best, clearing the hurdles!
それだけでもとなんで肺を噛む
Just from that, why bite my lungs?
すかさずにも目標を過保護修正して
Quickly adjusting my goals over-protectively,
大切なのは自分認めてくこと
The most important thing is to acknowledge yourself,
自分を許さなきゃ他人も許せない
If you don't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others.
Freedom! So you are lazy!
だって本当はcrazy!
Because I'm actually crazy!
はつじょうたちはそう
The ones in estrus are like that...
見えないところでバター足するんです
Fluttering their legs where they can't be seen.
本能に順従忠実
Obedient and faithful to instinct,
本能を縦横承知
Knowing instincts inside and out.
前頭よようなし
The prefrontal cortex is useless,
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
Which is why we take a break sometimes.
最初はグー！じゃんけんぽい！
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
決まったぜ！
We nailed it!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
めっちゃ楽しかったよ！
It was so much fun!
というわけでですね、記念ボイスとグッズを続けてお届けしました！
So, we've presented the commemorative voice and goods!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
では、いよいよ本格的に配信もがちラストスパートとなりました！
Now, the stream is finally entering the final stretch!
ここで重大なお知らせが2点あります！まずは皆さんご存知、沙花叉クロエ活動2周年記念グッズ！
First, as you all know, Sakamata Chloe's 2nd anniversary goods!
沙花叉クロエ 活動2周年記念
[Sakamata Chloe 2nd Anniversary]
はい、アクリルスタンドですね！
Yes, the acrylic stand!
アクリルスタンド
[Acrylic Stand]
クロエとおそろいフード付きタオル
[Chloe Matching Hooded Towel]
はい、クロエとおそろいフード付きタオル！
Yes, the Chloe-matching hooded towel!
サコッシュ
[Sacoche]
サコッシュです！
It's a sacoche!
片側が透明になっていますんで、
One side is transparent,
アクスタとか缶バッジとか、ま、そういうものもね、入れられますので、
so you can put things like acrylic stands or badges in it,
ぜひオタクグッズとしても活用してみてくだしゃい。
please use it as otaku merchandise as well!
そして、こちら！
And, here!
ああ、ついに来ちゃったんですね。
Ah, it's finally here.
イヌが、ぬいぐるみマスコットとなりました！
The dog has become a plush mascot!
ついにイヌモリスか。
Finally, an inumori.
なんか、イヌがなるのムカつくな、と思うんですけど、
I feel kind of annoyed that it's a dog,
やっぱり可愛いらしいので、ちょっと沙花叉ね、サコッシュとかも組み合わせてもいいかな、とか思うし、
but it's still cute, so I think it might be nice to combine it with Sakamata's sacoche.
なんか普通にね、沙花叉のイヌとかフレンドのイヌとかありますよね。そういうのとうまく合わせても、まあ、可愛いのかな、とは思いますね。
And you know, there are usually Sakamata dogs or friend dogs, right? Combining it with those would be cute too, I think.
はい。
Yes.
じめめたくなるような可愛さです。
It's cuteness that makes you want to keep it.
そして最後もこちら！
And lastly, this one!
はい、シチュエーションボイス「君とのサイン」。
Yes, the situational voice "A Sign with You."
内容はですね、ちょっとこのライブを見た方に、やっぱりね、ちょっと伝えたいなというのがあって、少し確信要素みたいなものがあるの。
The content is something I really want to convey to everyone who watched this live, so there are a few subtle hints hidden inside.
よかったら聞いてみてください。
Please take a listen if you'd like.
そして、これを全部ね、含めたフルセットをご購入いただいた方にはこちらです。
And for those who purchase the full set containing all of these, here it is!
はい、直筆サイン入りスタッフ風カード。
Yes, a staff-style card with a handwritten signature.
こちら（笑）。
Here it is (laughs).
こちらね、スタッフパスとなっております。
This is a staff pass.
ね、可愛いですよね。ちょっとフェスのスタッフパスっぽくて、めちゃめちゃ良いでしょ。
Right, it's cute, isn't it? It feels like a festival staff pass, which is super nice.
なんか自分スタッフなのだ！撮りますね、みたいな感じでやってください。
You can pretend like, "I'm staff!" or something like that.
あの、本当のフェスでは絶対に入らないでくださいね。
Please don't actually do that at a real festival, though!
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you.
めちゃめちゃ良いです。
It's super cool.
直筆サインもね、今回数量限定なしなので、ていうか1回もしたことないですけど。
And since there's no quantity limit for the handwritten signature this time—well, I've never done it before though.
はい、なしなので、安心してご購入ください。
Yes, there's no limit, so please purchase with confidence.
あと、もう1個あるのかな、何だっけ、もう1個ありますよね。何でしたっけ？
And, what else was there... what was it again?
特典ボイスですね（笑）。
It's the bonus voice! (Laughs)
特典ボイスはですね、沙花叉からの秘密のメッセージということでですね、こちらはちょっと答え合わせ風というか、まあ、ちょっと通常ボイスに近いものではあるんですけど、より特別感のあふれたボイスとなっておりますので、ぜひ聞いてください。
The bonus voice is a secret message from Sakamata, which is kind of like an answer-matching style—well, it's similar to normal voice tracks, but with an extra special vibe, so please be sure to listen to it!
はい、というわけで、グッズのお知らせでした！
And that wraps up the merchandise announcement!
もう1つのお知らせがあるんですけど、そちらはみんなの近くで伝えたいなと思うので、ちょっと移動します。
There's one more announcement, but I want to tell everyone up close, so let's move a bit.
はい、というわけで、もう1つのお知らせはですね、
Alright, so the other announcement is...
なんと！沙花叉クロヱオリジナル曲リリース決定です！すげー！
It's the release of Sakamata Chloe's original song! Awesome!
今回の曲はですね、作詞が、沙花叉、猫ハッカーさんに作曲をしていただいております。
This song features lyrics by Sakamata and composition by Neko Hacker.
非常にね、かわいらしくてノリもいい曲なので、ぜひ覚えてほしいなっていうのと、あのTikTokバスを狙ってます。よろしくお願いします。
It's a super cute and catchy song, so I really want you all to learn it, and I'm aiming for TikTok virality. Please support it!
はい、TikTokの方、皆さんよろしくお願いします。はい、22時10分からね、MVプレミアム公開もされますので、
Everyone, please check out TikTok. And starting at 22:10, the MV premiere will also be available,
よろしくお願いします。というわけで、こちらのステージで！
so please look forward to it. With that said, on this stage—
初披露させていただきたいと思います！
I'd like to perform it for the very first time!
じゃあ、いいですか、準備できてますか、皆さん？いきますよ！
Are you ready? Is everyone ready? Here we go!
最後、終わり曲、右左君君右下目上きゅるんめちょかわです！
And finally, the last song: "Right, Left, You, You, Right, Bottom, Look Up, So Damn Cute!"
左右君君右下目上きゅるんめちょかわ！
Right, left, you, you, right, bottom, look up, so damn cute!
あれやこれや言ったって結局要は面図じゃん？
ずっと傍に居るなんて正直前提じゃん？あぁ
No matter what anyone says, looks are what matter most in the end, right?
Always being by your side is basically a given, right? Ah...
あの子よりも上だって大体背伸びどんぐりじゃん？
マジな話かみだってリュックの中身パンパンじゃん？
Thinking you're better than that girl is just stretching like an acorn, right?
Honestly speaking, your backpack is stuffed full, right?
でもでも君となら 目指すまっすぐでひた向きで
心掴む理想の子に
Even so, if I'm with you, aiming straight ahead with single-minded devotion, grabbing your heart inside the ideal person's depth...
見て？頭の先から爪先まで
君好みのカスタムスタイル
Look? From the top of my head to the tips of my toes,
It's a custom style just the way you like it.
網子に乗って落ち込んで
泣いちゃう日もあるけど
Getting caught in the ropes and falling down,
there are days when I cry, but—
さあロケラングレランきみだけ
Come on, rocket launcher, grenade launcher, just for you!
もう残弾あるだけ撃ち込め(どかーん！)
Shoot away with all the remaining ammo! (Boom!)
爆風もくふわ♡キメたら
Once you nail that fluffy blast wave,
文句はこれでないね？
There are no complaints left, right?
左右君君右下目上きゅるんめちょかわ！(ふわふわ！)
Right, left, you, you, right, bottom, look up, so damn cute! (Fluffy fluffy!)
斜め右あざとさ舌ペろマジ顔もめっちゃかわいい！
Glancing up-right, acting cute with a tongue-poke—seriously, even her face is super cute!
夜ふかし極めて逆に健康だ
Mastering staying up late is actually healthy in reverse.
「宿題日過ぎてます！」
"My homework is past due!"
「炎上だけは勘弁です！」
"Please, anything but getting cancelled!"
そう言われても約束できない
Even if you say that, I can't promise anything,
好きな事だけ爆速でいたい
I just want to speed through doing what I love.
「そんな所も大好きです！」
"I love those parts about you too!"
「今日も生きててえらちゃんです！」
"You did a great job just surviving today!"
そう褒められると申し訳ない… 期待下回った人間です…
I feel guilty being praised like that... I'm someone who fell short of expectations...
でもでもでもでも君だから
But, but, but, but because it's you,
誓うまっすぐにひたむきに 心から揺らす君の為に
I swear, straight and devoted, for your sake, shaking from the bottom of my heart,
ほら頭の先から爪まで 君好みのナチュラルスタイル
Look, from the top of my head down to my claws, your favorite natural style,
うさちゃんパジャマのままだし ５度寝する日もあるけど
Staying in bunny pajamas, though there are days I hit snooze five times,
でもいつでもエイムは君タゲ
Still, my aim is always locked on you.
もう残弾ないけど撃ち抜け(ずきゅーん！)
I'm out of ammo, but shoot right through (Bang!)
「帽子に載っても良いよね？」
"It's fine if I sit on your hat, right?"
「文句は後で聞きます…」
"I'll hear your complaints later..."
右左君君右上目きゅるんめんちょかわかわ？(ふわふわ！)
Right, left, you, you, up, right, up-gazing, sparkling, super cute? (Fluffy!)
斜め右あざとさ舌ペろマジ顔もめっちゃかわいい！
Glancing up-right, acting cute with a tongue-poke—seriously, even her face is super cute!
2周年ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for 2 years!
3周年目も みんなよろちゃんです！楽しかった、ありがとう！
For the 3rd year too, please take care of us everyone! It was fun, thank you!